//選択肢問題の配列
let questions = [
  {
    number: 1,
    question: "config",
    answer: "設定",
    options: ["設定", "安全", "対策", "問題"],
  },
  {
    number: 2,
    question: "immediate",
    answer: "即時の",
    options: ["挿入する", "即時の", "退去", "隣接"],
  },
  {
    number: 3,
    question: "trace",
    answer: "痕跡",
    options: ["痕跡", "交通", "交換", "トラック"],
  },
  {
    number: 4,
    question: "adjacent",
    answer: "隣接した",
    options: ["設定", "安全", "対策", "隣接した"],
  },
  {
    number: 5,
    question: "insert",
    answer: "挿入する",
    options: ["設定", "挿入する", "対策", "問題"],
  },
  {
    number: 6,
    question: "exit",
    answer: "退去",
    options: ["設定", "安全", "退去", "問題"],
  },
  {
    number: 7,
    question: "queue",
    answer: "待っている列",
    options: ["設定", "安全", "待っている列", "問題"],
  },
  {
    number: 8,
    question: "instructor",
    answer: "指導者",
    options: ["設定", "安全", "構造体", "指導者"],
  },
  {
    number: 9,
    question: "replay",
    answer: "再試合",
    options: ["再試合", "安全", "対策", "問題"],
  },
  {
    number: 10,
    question: "cat",
    answer: "猫",
    options: ["設定", "安全", "対策", "猫"],
  },
];
